

ABOUT ME

I am a Junior Full Stack Developer with experience in web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, and advanced proficiency in frameworks and libraries like React and Node.js. I have knowledge in SQL databases and backend implementation TypeScript.

CONTACT

678567628

annahico@gmail.com

Barcelona Ciudad

Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

STAKS

• HTML5

REACT

CSS3

• MYSQL

JAVASCRIPT
MONGODB

• GIT

• EXPRESS

TYPESCRIPT

• GITHUB

NODE.JS

BOOTSTRAP

LANGUAGES

- Catalan Native
- · Spanish Native
- English C2
- German A2



HIDALGO COSTA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER

CONSORCI BARCELONA

2022 - 2024

Teach English language skills (reading, writing and speaking) to secondary and high school students. Prepare and adapt educational materials, evaluating academic progress. Foster an inclusive and motivating learning environment.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

ETT

2015-2022

Provide support and solutions to customer queries, ensuring customer satisfaction. Manage and resolve complaints efficiently. Maintain accurate and up-to-date records of customer interactions.

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP FULL STACK DEVELOPER

GeeksHubs

UNIVERSITY MASTER'S DEGREE IN EDUCATION AND ICT

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, UOC

UNIVERSITY MASTER'S DEGREE TEACHER TRAINING

Blanquerna, URL

2022

POSTGRADUATE EDUCATIONAL DIRECTION AND **LEADERSHIP**

Universitat Oberta de Catalunya, UOC

DEGREE IN ENGLISH STUDIES

Universitat de Barcelona, UB 2015-2020

ERASMUS 2018-2019

PROJECTS

Booking Final Project Interactive TV Project Restaurant Menu Project **Shopping Cart**

Back-end Project

Front-end Project